Finding Aid for Michigan Daily Records, 1950-2006
Bentley Historical Library
- Negatives-Chronological, 1963-1980; 4.5 linear feet
  - 1971
    - July-December
      - Car Bash, 10/28/1971 (Box 3)
        (Knox)
      - City Council, 11/01/1971 (Box 3)
        (Margolick)
      - Speeches in Prison Reform, 11/06/1971 (Box 3)
      - Pioneer High School, 11/07/1971 (Box 3)
      - Rhodes at Coffee Talk, 11/10/1971 (Box 3)
      - Ozone House, 11/11/1971 (Box 3)
      - SGC Selections, Polling Places, Misc. Diag, 11/17/1971 (Box 3)
      - Women's Meeting, 11/12/1971 (Box 3)
        (Krullich)
      - Dome, 11/18/1971 (Box 3)
      - SACUA, 12/05/1971 (Box 3)
      - Trotter House, 12/07/1971 (Box 3)
  - 1972
    - January-December
      - Irish Rally Ire, 01/04/1972 (Box 3)
        (Upton)
      - Rally Protesting British in, 01/04/1972 (Box 3)
      - Assistant Dean Witke, 01/12/1972 (Box 3)
      - Mayor Harris vs. TV, 01/12/1972 (Box 3)
      - School Bd. Pres. McPherson, 01/21/1972 (Box 3)
      - Course Meet, Student Counseling Office, 01/24/1972 (Box 3)
      - PESC Meeting, 01/25/1972 (Box 3)
      - CPHA Strikers, 02/08/1972 (Box 3)
      - Pi Lambda Phi Frat House, 02/14/1972 (Box 3)
      - Detroit Guerrilla Theater, 02/18/1972 (Box 3)
      - Women Protest Alimony, 02/24/1972 (Box 3)
      - Plant Strike, 02/25/1972 (Box 3)
      - Women in Law Quad, 02/28/1972 (Box 3)
      - Marine Recruiter and Lone Demonstrator, 03/15/1972 (Box 3)
      - ?, 03/23/1972 (Box 3)
      - Burstein (Boorstin?), 04/03/1972 (Box 3)
      - Prison Warden, 04/05/1972 (Box 3)
      - Kelsey Museum, 04/07/1972 (Box 3)
      - Office of Student services, 04/11/1972 (Box 3)
      - Administration Building, 04/12/1972 (Box 3)
      - Diag Peace Rally, 04/12/1972 (Box 3)
      - Students Confront Feldkamp, 04/12/1972 (Box 3)
      - Chinese Ping Pong, 04/14/1972 (Box 3)
      - Ping Pong, 04/15/1972 (Box 3)
      - Wart Protest and Harris Sit-in, 04/16/1972 (Box 3)
      - Student Strike Meeting, 04/19/1972 (Box 3)
      - Four People Arrested for Digging Bomb Craters on U Property, 06/05/1972 (Box 3)
      - 4th Ave Adult News, 7/72 (Box 3)
      - Courtroom, 7/72 (Box 3)
      - St. Joseph Hospital, 07/18/1972 (Box 3)
      - Registration, 09/06/1972 (Box 3)
      - National Guard Armory, 09/07/1972 (Box 3)
      - Cable TV Installers, 09/26/1972 (Box 3)
      - Wherehouse Bust, 10/17/1972 (Box 3)
        (Tessem.)
      - Demonstrators at Ambassador Bridge, 11/06/1972 (Box 3)
      - Demonstrators Against War, 11/06/1972 (Box 3)
      - Anti-War Demonstrators, Detroit Bridge, 11/06/1972 (Box 3)
      - Anti-War Demonstrators Bridge, 11/06/1972 (Box 3)
      - Ms. Parker, 11/15/1972 (Box 3)
      - Rape Conference, 12/02/1972 (Box 3)
      - Mrs. Lansing, 12/07/1972 (Box 3)
  - 1973
    - January-December
      - Richard Wilbur, Poet par Excellence at Hopwood, 01/02/1973 (Box 3)
      - Prof. Werner Landecker, 02/16/1973 (Box 3)
      - Anglican Orchestra, 03/21/1973 (Box 3)
      - Smoking Dope, 03/21/1973 (Box 3)
      - Aeolian Chamber Players, 03/24/1973 (Box 3)
        (Kasmauski)
      - Ann Arbor Houses Exterior and Excellence at Hopwood, 03/26/1973 (Box 3)
        (Hollander)
      - Women's Libbers at Ann Arbor City Council, 03/31/1973 (Box 3)
      - Hash Fest, 04/01/1973 (Box 3)
      - Burning a Book on Diag, 04/11/1973 (Box 3)
      - Opera at Mendelssohn, 04/11/1973 (Box 3)
      - Burton Tower, 04/12/1973 (Box 3)
      - Daily Libel vs. WCBN, 04/14/1973 (Box 3)
      - Tony's and Margie, 04/18/1973 (Box 3)
      - Afro Center, 04/18/1973 (Box 3)
      - Sec. Strike, 04/30/1973 (Box 3)
      - TV Center, 05/09/1973 (Box 3)
      - Tuition Strike rally in LSA, 09/28/1973 (Box 3)
      - Orr Guy(?), 09/29/1973 (Box 3)
        (Fink)
      - Bimbo's, 09/29/1973 (Box 3)
      - ROTC Sign, 10/02/1973 (Box 3)
      - Hilbish and U Symphony, 10/17/1973 (Box 3)
      - W.H. Auden's Ex-House, 10/18/1973 (Box 3)
      - Honk for Impeachment, 10/22/1973 (Box 3)
      - Xanadu Co-op, 11/01/1973 (Box 3)
      - City Council, 11/05/1973 (Box 3)
      - Free Art and "Underwear Protest", 11/09/1973 (Box 3)
      - Union Magazine S, 11/28/1973 (Box 3)
        (Kagam)
  - 1974
    - January-December
      - Blues and Jazz Fest (Sun Ra), 1974 undated (Box 3)
      - Fleming Takes Japs' $, 01/22/1974 (Box 3)
      - Honk for Impeachment, 2/74 (Box 3)
      - Exxon Demonstration, 02/06/1974 (Box 3)
      - Senior Sports Staff, 02/07/1974 (Box 3)
      - Reuther, 02/13/1974 (Box 3)
        (Lubens)
      - GEO, 02/27/1974 (Box 3)
        (Gottlieb/Lubens)
      - City Council Meeting, 02/19/1974 (Box 3)
        (Ruttan)
      - Cop Ticketing Bicycle, 09/10/1973 (Box 3)
      - Kung Fu Karate, 02/28/1974 (Box 3)
      - Ann Arbor Film Fest, 03/12/1974 (Box 3)
      - Landlords in Ann Arbor, 03/12/1974 (Box 3)
      - U Power Center, 03/13/1974 (Box 3)
      - Quasar Radio Telescope, 09/20/1973 (Box 3)
        (Upton, Joan)
      - Fire Station #5 Fire Truck, 03/15/1974 (Box 3)
      - HRP Candidates, 03/17/1974 (Box 3)
      - Impeach Nixon Party, 03/23/1974 (Box 3)
      - Herb David Guitar Shop, 03/27/1974 (Box 3)
      - Kathak-N. Indian Dance, 04/03/1974 (Box 3)
      - Impeach Nixon Rally, 04/03/1974 (Box 3)
      - Impeach Nixon Rally, 04/03/1974 (Box 3)
      - Japanese Dance& Music Group, 04/06/1974 (Box 3)
      - Nixon visit to Michigan, 04/10/1974 (Box 3)
      - Nixon in Michigan, 04/10/1974 (Box 3)
      - Crucible, 04/10/1974 (Box 3)
      - Crucible, 04/10/1974 (Box 3)
      - Cheerleaders Trying Out, 04/12/1974 (Box 3)
      - Farmers Market, 04/13/1974 (Box 3)
      - Logos Book Store, 04/17/1974 (Box 3)
      - Grad. Lib., E & W Stacks, Renovation, etc., 05/08/1974 (Box 3)
      - Regents, 05/16/1974 (Box 3)
      - Library Ball, 05/13/1974 (Box 3)
      - School Board Winners, 06/01/1974 (Box 3)
      - Inglis House, 06/04/1974 (Box 3)
      - Extensions, 06/05/1974 (Box 3)
      - Ann Arbor Restaurants, 06/06/1974 (Box 3)
      - Briarwood, 06/07/1974 (Box 3)
      - New A & D Building, 07/18/1974 (Box 3)
      - Humane Society, 07/24/1974 (Box 3)
      - Medieval(?) Festival, 08/04/1974 (Box 3)
        (Kagan)
      - Blues and Jazz, 09/06/1974 (Box 3)
      - B.B. King B&J Fest, 09/08/1974 (Box 3)
      - B.B. King, Luther Allison, Sunnyland Slim, JR. Walker, Blues and Jazz Fest, 09/08/1974 (Box 3)
      - B.B. King, Blues and Jazz Fest, 09/08/1974 (Box 3)
      - Luther Allison and Beeg Saxman, B&J Fest, 09/08/1974 (Box 3)
      - Daily Mass Meeting, 09/12/1974 (Box 3)
      - UFW Rally (Diag) Delores Huerta, 09/12/1974 (Box 3)
      - H.M.S. Pinafore, 09/12/1974 (Box 3)
      - Dexter, MI, circa 9/20/74 (Box 3)
      - Geo. P. Wheeler Bridge, 09/25/1974 (Box 3)
      - Marvelous Esch and Local Politicos and Bursley at Spaghetti Fundraiser, 09/25/1974 (Box 3)
      - Rick Parks, Security Guard at E. Quad, 09/28/1974 (Box 3)
      - Day Care Center, 10/13/1974 (Box 3)
      - Alvin Ailey, 10/18/1974 (Box 3)
      - Regents Candidates, 10/23/1974 (Box 3)
      - MUD Bowl, 10/26/1974 (Box 3)
      - Ozone Parade, 10/25/1974 (Box 3)
      - Ozone Parade, 10/25/1974 (Box 3)
      - Ozone Parade, 10/25/1974 (Box 3)
      - Chances Are, 10/26/1974 (Box 3)
        (Sheiner)
      - Aerosmith, 11/74 (Box 3)
      - Dem Hderts(?) Eckstein, 11/05/1974 (Box 3)
      - Damn Yankee's Preview in Rehearsal, 11/07/1974 (Box 3)
      - Nixon Snow Man, 11/16/1974 (Box 3)
      - Maxey Boys Training School, 11/16/1974 (Box 3)
      - GEO Folks on Diag, 11/25/1974 (Box 3)
        (Benedict)
      - GEO Folks on Diag, 11/25/1974 (Box 3)
      - U. Hospital, 12/04/1975 (Box 3)
  - 1975
    - January-June
      - Angus Campbell Director ISR, 07/01/1968 (Box 4)
      - Mariposa, 1975 (Box 4)
      - Mariposa, 1975 (Box 4)
      - Mariposa, 1975 (Box 4)
      - Mariposa, 1975 (Box 4)
      - Mariposa, 1975 (Box 4)
      - Commencement, 1975 (Box 4)
      - Commencement, 1975 (Box 4)
      - Commencement, 1975 (Box 4)
      - Commencement, 1975 (Box 4)
      - Winter Registration, 01/08/1975 (Box 4)
      - Jean Luc Ponty(?), 02/20/1975 (Box 4)
      - String Quartet, 01/08/1975 (Box 4)
      - Crowd at Social Services for Food Stamps, 01/09/1975 (Box 4)
      - Brown Jug Strike, 01/11/1975 (Box 4)
      - Pilot Students and Dean Frye, 01/22/1975 (Box 4)
      - Pilot Program Meeting, 01/23/1975 (Box 4)
      - Police Communications System, 01/27/1975 (Box 4)
      - Anti-ROTC Meeting, 01/29/1975 (Box 4)
      - Women's Commission Meeting, 01/29/1975 (Box 4)
      - ROTC Protest Diag, 02/03/1975 (Box 4)
      - Vote to Strike GEO Meeting, 02/05/1975 (Box 4)
      - Legal Aid, 02/05/1975 (Box 4)
      - New Tennis, Track Building, 02/05/1975 (Box 4)
      - Eastwind Children's Workshop, 02/07/1975 (Box 4)
      - GEO Vote Announcement and Methodist Church, 02/10/1975 (Box 4)
      - GEO Voting, 02/10/1975 (Box 4)
      - GEO Strike, 02/11/1975 (Box 4)
      - GEO Soup Kitchen, 02/11/1975 (Box 4)
      - Closed Signs on Deli, 02/12/1975 (Box 4)
      - GEO Demonstration, 02/14/1975 (Box 4)
      - GEO Demonstration, 02/14/1975 (Box 4)
      - GEO Undergrad Support Meeting, 02/14/1975 (Box 4)
      - Rackham Bomb, 02/14/1975 (Box 4)
      - Conference Against Racism, 02/14/1975-02/16/1975 (Box 4)
      - Conference Against Racism, 02/14/1975-02/16/1975 (Box 4)
      - Conference Against Racism, 02/14/1975-02/16/1975 (Box 4)
      - Conference Against Racism, 02/14/1975-02/16/1975 (Box 4)
      - Conference Against Racism, 02/14/1975-02/16/1975 (Box 4)
      - Conference Against Racism, 02/14/1975-02/16/1975 (Box 4)
      - Conference Against Racism, 02/14/1975-02/16/1975 (Box 4)
      - Bells at Burton Bell Tower, 02/15/1975 (Box 4)
      - Third World Coalition Takes Over Ad Building, 02/18/1975 (Box 4)
      - Demo at Ad Building, Black Over Ad Building, 02/19/1975 (Box 4)
      - GEO Picketers on N. Campus, 02/24/1975 (Box 4)
      - GEO Picketers on N. Campus, 02/24/1975 (Box 4)
      - GEO Rally in LSA Building, 02/24/1975 (Box 4)
      - Press Card, 02/27/1975 (Box 4)
      - City Council, 03/10/1975 (Box 4)
      - GEO Bargaining Team, 03/10/1975 (Box 4)
      - Ann Arbor Film Directors and Crowd at Door, 03/11/1975 (Box 4)
      - GEO Back-to-Work Vote, March 1, 1975 (Box 4)
      - Police Station with Tear Gas Equipment, 03/14/1975 (Box 4)
      - LSA Student Government, 03/19/1975 (Box 4)
      - M. Rostropovich M. Class, 03/21/1975 (Box 4)
      - Launching of "Peoples Yellow Pages", 03/31/1975 (Box 4)
      - Hash Bash, 04/01/1975 (Box 4)
      - Tales of Hoffman, 04/02/1975 (Box 4)
      - Tales of Hoffman, 04/02/1975 (Box 4)
      - Tales of Hoffman, 04/02/1975 (Box 4)
      - Martha Cook Tea, 04/04/1975 (Box 4)
      - CRISP, 04/07/1975 (Box 4)
      - City Council Meeting, 04/09/1975 (Box 4)
      - North Campus Commons, 04/09/1975 (Box 4)
      - Black Frats, Pres. of #1 Frat, 04/13/1975 (Box 4)
      - Fleming and Scholarship Recipients, 04/16/1975 (Box 4)
      - Tappan Hall Stairs, Firetraps, 05/07/1975 (Box 4)
      - Indian Demo Front of Ad Bldg, 05/13/1975 (Box 4)
      - Regents Meeting, 05/13/1975 (Box 4)
      - U-Cellar, 05/13/1975 (Box 4)
      - Fire on Tappan and Hill, 05/27/1975 (Box 4)
      - Soc. Services Welfare, 06/13/1975 (Box 4)
      - Carrilloneur, 06/16/1975 (Box 4)
      - Tenants Union, 06/17/1975 (Box 4)
    - July-December
      - Chicago Symphony String Quartet, 07/07/1975 (Box 4)
      - Tuition meeting, 07/22/1975 (Box 4)
      - Janitors (Play), 07/24/1975 (Box 4)
      - Schick Hitchhiking, 07/25/1975 (Box 4)
      - Kidnapped Kids and Mom, 09/08/1975 (Box 4)
      - Poison Mushroom, 09/12/1975 (Box 4)
      - Ethnic Fair, 09/13/1975 (Box 4)
      - Fruit Vendor, 09/15/1975 (Box 4)
      - Protest of Soviet Jew oppression, 09/29/1975 (Box 4)
      - Daily Libels, 09/29/1975 (Box 4)
      - Jeff Liebster(?), 09/30/1975 (Box 4)
      - Gerald Ford, 10/75 (Box 4)
      - Gerald Ford, 10/75 (Box 4)
      - Ars Musica and Organists at Michigan Theater, 10/01/1975 (Box 4)
      - Fall Art Fair, 10/03/1975 (Box 4)
      - Groundbreaking Ceremonies for Federal Building, 10/06/1975 (Box 4)
      - (Turque) Running in Woods, October 11, 1975 (Box 4)
      - All Directions (At Blind Pig), 10/17/1975 (Box 4)
      - Adult Book Store, 10/17/1975 (Box 4)
      - Women's Studies Committee Meeting, 10/24/1975 (Box 4)
      - WCBN, 10/29/1975 (Box 4)
      - SGC Tea with Fleming, 11/03/1975 (Box 4)
      - Fleming's House, 11/06/1975 (Box 4)
      - David Weir, 11/08/1975 (Box 4)
      - Diag Demo (CIA), 11/11/1975 (Box 4)
      - Machiavelli's "Celebration", 11/14/1975 (Box 4)
      - Paper Aeroplane Contest, 11/16/1975 (Box 4)
      - Daily Candids, 12/03/1975 (Box 4)
        (Fink/Lubens)
      - Farmers Market, 12/06/1975 (Box 4)
      - LSA/Student Government Election, Fishbowl, 02/08/1975 (Box 4)
  - 1976
    - January-June
      - Arthur Ashe, 01/05/1976 (Box 4)
        (Benjamin)
      - Esch/Protestors, 01/16/1976 (Box 4)
      - Book Sale Line for Ad, 01/20/1976 (Box 4)
        (Kaye)
      - Pet Cemetery, 01/21/1976 (Box 4)
      - Pet Cemetery, 01/21/1976 (Box 4)
      - Pet Cemetery, 01/21/1976 (Box 4)
      - Small Dorm, Henderson Hall, 01/30/1976 (Box 4)
      - Ford/Bussing Protestors, 01/31/1976 (Box 4)
      - Anti-CIA Demo and TU Speaking at Regents Meeting, 02/04/1976 (Box 4)
      - Martha Cook, 02/13/1976 (Box 4)
      - Beefalos, 02/25/1976 (Box 4)
      - AFSCME at Crisler, 02/26/1976 (Box 4)
      - Beefaloes, 02/26/1976 (Box 4)
      - Beefaloes, 02/26/1976 (Box 4)
      - WBCN DJ, 3/76 (Box 4)
      - New Daily Business Staff, 03/01/1976 (Box 4)
      - NSA/CIA Demo at City Council, 03/01/1976 (Box 4)
      - Steam Tunnels, 03/19/1976 (Box 4)
      - Bursley Bus Stop, 03/26/1976 (Box 4)
      - Derby Days, 03/26/1976 (Box 4)
      - Armstrong, Martin, Bogan, 03/27/1976 (Box 4)
      - Arab Demo, 03/31/1976 (Box 4)
      - Arab Demo, 03/31/1976 (Box 4)
      - Arab Demo, 03/31/1976 (Box 4)
      - GOP Headquarters, 04/05/1976 (Box 4)
      - Medicaid Cut Demonstration, 04/08/1976 (Box 4)
      - RC Player "The Tempest", 04/08/1976 (Box 4)
      - Community Switchboard, Ozone House, Drug Help, 04/09/1976 (Box 4)
      - GEO Demo, 04/09/1976 (Box 4)
      - Democratic Dinner, 04/10/1976 (Box 4)
      - Udall and Walpu(?), 04/10/1976 (Box 4)
      - Mayhews and Shapu, MSA, 04/13/1976 (Box 4)
      - Israel Rally Diag, 04/13/1976 (Box 4)
      - Reliable Realty Demo and Slum on Dips(?), 04/13/1976 (Box 4)
      - University Dancers Spring Concert, 06/14/1976 (Box 4)
      - Frizbee, 7/76 (Box 4)
        (McConnal)
    - September-December
      - Jazz and Blues 14, 09/09/1976 (Box 4)
      - Experimental Theater, 09/17/1976 (Box 4)
      - GEO, Picket on Diag, 09/20/1976 (Box 4)
      - UAW Pickets in Ypsi, 09/22/1976 (Box 4)
      - Chick Corea, 09/25/1976 (Box 4)
      - Chick Corea, 09/25/1976 (Box 4)
      - Fleming Giving out Faculty Awards, 09/27/1976 (Box 4)
      - PIRGIM Press Conference, 09/28/1976 (Box 4)
        (Schneider)
      - PIRGIM Press Conference, 09/28/1976 (Box 4)
      - Fleming's Tea, 09/29/1976 (Box 4)
      - Plant Sale at Union, 10/76 (Box 4)
      - Acting Company, 10/76 (Box 4)
        (Eccker)
      - Kissing Contest Second Chance 10/4/76 (Box 4)
      - Proposal A, Litter Pickup, 10/10/1976 (Box 4)
      - Othello, 10/12/1976 (Box 4)
      - Carter, 10/15/1976 (Box 4)
        (Blintzes)
      - Sheriff's Candidate Debate, 10/19/1976 (Box 4)
      - Attorney General Candidate, 10/20/1976 (Box 4)
      - Filipina Narcisco, Leona Perez, VA Nurses, 10/20/1976 (Box 4)
      - GEO Strike Vote, 10/25/1976 (Box 4)
      - Trueblood Theatre "What Every, 10/25/1976 (Box 4)
      - Car Smashing one U, 10/29/1976 (Box 4)
      - Democratic Headquarters Election Night, 11/02/1976 (Box 4)
      - Camelot, 11/03/1976 (Box 4)
      - Frisbee Fling, 11/19/1976 (Box 4)
      - After OSU Win, 11/21/1976 (Box 4)
      - Trotter House Food Drive, 11/23/1976 (Box 4)
      - Oh, What a Lovely War, 11/22/1976 (Box 4)
      - MSA Election, 11/30/1976 (Box 4)
      - Assault Crisis Center, 12/10/1976 (Box 4)
      - Elaine at Night for Rape Story, 12/10/1976 (Box 4)
      - GEO Protest in front of LSA, 10/31/1976 (Box 4)
  - 1977
    - January-June
      - Briarwood, 01/01/1977 (Box 4)
      - Briarwood, 01/01/1977 (Box 4)
      - Briarwood, 01/01/1977 (Box 4)
        (Bilinsky.)
      - Rose Bowl Parade, 01/01/1977 (Box 4)
      - Rose Bowl Parade, 01/01/1977 (Box 4)
      - Rose Bowl Parade, 01/01/1977 (Box 4)
      - Rose Bowl Parade, 01/01/1977 (Box 4)
      - Rose Bowl, 01/01/1977 (Box 4)
      - Sunday Magazine, Gambling, 01/14/1977 (Box 4)
      - Daily People and Passports, 01/17/1977 (Box 4)
      - South Americans at Ark, 01/20/1977 (Box 4)
        (Knox, John)
      - Downtown, Ann Arbor, 01/27/1977 (Box 4)
      - Food Co-op, Washtenaw Jail, 01/30/1977 (Box 4)
      - E.S.P. Experts, New Daily Editors, 01/31/1977 (Box 4)
      - Bentley Library, Govindas, 01/31/1977 (Box 4)
      - Maxinov / Mott's Childrens Hospital Intensive Care Ward, 02/07/1977 (Box 4)
      - Mr. Tanys(?) Picket, 02/07/1977 (Box 4)
      - Hair, 02/14/1977 (Box 4)
      - Jean Luc Ponty, 02/20/1977 (Box 4)
      - Sunday Mas, Holden Center for Preemies, 17 mo. old Baby and Family, 02/22/1977 (Box 4)
      - Ypsi Porno Sports, 02/25/1977 (Box 4)
      - AFSCME, 02/23/1977 (Box 4)
      - AFSCME, 02/23/1977 (Box 4)
      - AFSCME, 02/23/1977 (Box 4)
      - Union Strike, 02/25/1977 (Box 4)
      - Wheeler/AFSCME President and Garbage Truck Picket, 02/28/1977 (Box 4)
      - Abdel Roodenko, War Resistance League, 3/77 (Box 4)
      - GEO Pickets, 03/18/1977 (Box 4)
      - Mr. Bursley, 03/21/1977 (Box 4)
      - AFSCME Contract Signing, 03/24/1977 (Box 4)
      - Parade and Derby Days, 03/25/1977 (Box 4)
      - Ramsey Lewis, 03/25/1977 (Box 4)
      - Music Man, 03/30/1977 (Box 4)
      - MSA Candidates A Cuts, 03/30/1977 (Box 4)
      - Republicans on Election Night at Holiday Inn, 04/04/1977 (Box 4)
      - Dance, 04/04/1977 (Box 4)
      - Married Students, 04/06/1977 (Box 4)
      - Ford Lecture Rackham, 04/06/1977 (Box 4)
      - Ford, Football Practice, Schembechler, 04/07/1977 (Box 4)
      - Knox Ford at Football Practice, 4/7/77 (Box 4)
      - Egg Drop, 04/08/1977 (Box 4)
      - Egg Drop, 04/08/1977 (Box 4)
      - Egg Drop, 04/08/1977 (Box 4)
      - PBB (Farmer Ect), 04/13/1977 (Box 4)
        (Ades)
      - Motts Childrens Hospital Clowns, 04/11/1977 (Box 4)
      - Ward Winners Swearing in, 04/14/1977 (Box 4)
      - Language Lab, 04/15/1977 (Box 4)
      - Fruit Vendors, 05/06/1977 (Box 4)
      - Archaeology Exhibit, 05/07/1977 (Box 4)
      - Solar Energy Receptor, Passports, Corky Segal Album Cover, Arb and Cement Slabs, 05/12/1977 (Box 4)
      - Gary Burton, 05/13/1977 (Box 4)
      - Farmers Market, 05/16/1977 (Box 4)
      - "Anastasia" (Play), 05/17/1977 (Box 4)
      - Regents Meeting, 05/19/1977 (Box 4)
      - Museum of Science, 05/20/1977 (Box 4)
      - Barbour Gym and Luci Titunuk(?) Astrologist, 05/25/1977 (Box 4)
      - Greek Festival Dancers, 06/02/1977 (Box 4)
      - S. African Peoples Ambassador 6/2/77 (Box 4)
      - Condemned Housing and Passport, 06/02/1977 (Box 4)
      - Business Staff, Bell Tower, Cube, Dental School, 06/03/1977 (Box 4)
      - Pottery Guild Annual Sale, 06/05/1977 (Box 4)
        (Schneider, Chris)
      - Peace Neighborhood Center, Garden Plots, Linda and David Koski, 06/06/1977 (Box 4)
      - Fred Dittmer, Beekeeper, 06/17/1977 (Box 4)
      - Fred Dittmer, Beekeeper, 06/17/1977 (Box 4)
      - Beer Collection, 06/18/1977 (Box 4)
    - July-December
      - Free Art, Fuller Pool, 07/06/1977 (Box 4)
      - Federal Building, Post Office, 07/07/1977 (Box 4)
      - AatA Bus Drivers strike, 07/12/1977 (Box 4)
      - Transportation Employees Union Protests at City Hall, 07/15/1977 (Box 4)
      - Ferency and Art Fair, 07/21/1977 (Box 4)
        (Alan)
      - Art Fair, 07/21/1977 (Box 4)
      - Medieval Fest, Ark Lawn, 07/31/1977 (Box 4)
      - "Dungeons and Dragons", 08/03/1977 (Box 4)
      - Earl at Typesetting Machines, 08/03/1977 (Box 4)
      - Anti Nuke Demo, Fermi II Site, 08/06/1977 (Box 4)
      - Anti Nuke Demo, Fermi 11, 08/06/1977 (Box 4)
      - Anti Nuke Demo, Fermi II Site, 08/06/1977 (Box 4)
      - Chamber Music at Union, 08/08/1977 (Box 4)
      - U Cellar, 08/11/1977 (Box 4)
      - Moving In (Parents), 09/06/1977 (Box 4)
        (Freeberg)
      - Buying Books at U Cellar, 09/07/1977 (Box 4)
      - Buying Books at Cellar, 09/07/1977 (Box 4)
      - Lines, Fainter, Vicky Prepich, 09/07/1977 (Box 4)
      - Student in Library, 09/09/1977 (Box 4)
      - Flood's Bar and T-Shirts, 09/07/1977 (Box 4)
      - T-Shirts and Cabbie and Floods Bar, 09/07/1977 (Box 4)
      - Governors Conference, 09/08/1977 (Box 4)
      - Governors Conference, 09/08/1977 (Box 4)
      - Governors Conference, 09/08/1977 (Box 4)
      - Governors Conference, 09/08/1977 (Box 4)
      - "Tent-in" at SAB, 09/08/1977 (Box 4)
      - Kent St. Protest, 09/09/1977 (Box 4)
      - Old St. Joseph Auction, 09/10/1977 (Box 4)
      - Kiwanis Sale Fall 177, 09/10/1977 (Box 4)
      - Ethnic Festival, 09/10/1977 (Box 4)
      - Mirage Women Dancers, 09/12/1977 (Box 4)
      - L-S Club, 09/13/1977 (Box 4)
      - Fishbowl Poster Sale, 09/14/1977 (Box 4)
      - Sculpture by Ginnever, 09/14/1977 (Box 4)
      - Marching, 09/15/1977 (Box 4)
      - Marching, 09/15/1977 (Box 4)
      - Matching, 09/15/1977 (Box 4)
      - Marching, 09/15/1977 (Box 4)
      - Regents Meeting, 09/15/1977 (Box 4)
      - New Dawn Water Bed Stuffing, 09/16/1977 (Box 4)
      - Fencing Demo on Diag, 09/16/1977 (Box 4)
      - Frisbee Jamboree, 09/18/1977 (Box 4)
      - Preacher John, Diag, Daily Mass Meeting, 09/21/1977 (Box 4)
      - Maria with Ice Cream Cone, 09/21/1977 (Box 4)
      - Marching, 09/22/1977 (Box 4)
      - Bulls and M.B., 09/22/1977 (Box 4)
      - South African Demo on Diag, 09/23/1977 (Box 4)
      - Jodi Braxton, Marion Brown, 09/24/1977 (Box 4)
      - Paper Box of the Year(?), 09/27/1977 (Box 4)
      - CRISP Lines, Student Activities, Lacrosse, 09/29/1977 (Box 4)
      - Bulh(?) Building, 09/30/1977 (Box 4)
      - Gospel on Steps of Diag, 09/30/1977 (Box 4)
      - Johnny Orr Addresses President's Club, 10/01/1977 (Box 4)
      - Humane Society Book Sale, 10/06/1977 (Box 4)
      - Aztec Dancers, 10/11/1977 (Box 4)
      - Beach Women "Mas" (?), 10/13/1977 (Box 4)
      - Huron Towers, 10/13/1977 (Box 4)
      - No Nuke Detroit Rally, 10/15/1977 (Box 4)
      - No Nuke Detroit Rally, 10/15/1977 (Box 4)
      - Hill Area Ethnic Food Day, 10/10/1977 (Box 4)
      - Highland Park, 10/20/1977 (Box 4)
      - Senior Citizen Medical Fair, 10/22/1977 (Box 4)
      - Bubble Gum, 10/24/1977 (Box 4)
      - Fake Train Wreck, 10/26/1977 (Box 4)
      - Fake Train Wreck, 10/26/1977 (Box 4)
      - Blind T.A., 10/27/1977 (Box 4)
      - Ozone Parade, 10/28/1977 (Box 4)
      - Halloween Free Art, 10/31/1977 (Box 4)
      - Blood Bank at Markley, 11/01/1977 (Box 4)
      - Basketball Bounce on Diag, 11/04/1977 (Box 4)
      - Gerald Ford at Pres. Papers Building, 11/04/1977 (Box 4)
      - Frank Zappa, 11/06/1977 (Box 4)
      - Pool Sharks Mich. Union, 11/08/1977 (Box 4)
      - U of M Lawyers Club, Diabetes Testing, M on Diag, 11/09/1977 (Box 4)
      - S. Africa Investment Lecture, 11/09/1977 (Box 4)
      - White Elephant Sale, 11/11/1977 (Box 4)
      - Regents Tour, S.Q., 11/17/1977 (Box 4)
      - Regents Tour, S.Q., 11/17/1977 (Box 4)
      - MSA, 11/18/1977 (Box 4)
        (Serling)
      - Wipe Ohio State Toilet Paper, 11/18/1977 (Box 4)
      - Modern Dance, 11/21/1977 (Box 4)
      - Parade Floats 11, 11/21/1977 (Box 4)
      - Parade Floats #2, 11/21/1977 (Box 4)